ABC Circle Films Production Records for the Mini Series War and Remembrance PASC.0103
UCLA Library Special Collections
ABC Circle Films production records for the mini-series War and Remembrance
1984-1988
UCLA Library Special Collections
ABC Circle Films
PASC.0103
9.0 Linear Feet (18 boxes)
Based on Herman Wouk's novel, the television mini-series War and Remembrance is the story of WWII and its effects on Navy officer Pug Henry and his family. The collection consists of production records and research files related to the production.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Keith Burns, 1991.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9942302893606533
Biography/History
Based on Herman Wouk's novel, the television mini-series War and Remembrance is the story of WWII and its effects on Navy officer Pug Henry and his family. The 7 part series was co-produced by ABC Circle Films and Dan Curtis Productions, was produced by Barbara Steele, and co-written by Earl W. Wallace, Herman Wouk, and Dan Curtis.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of production records and research files related to the television mini-series, War and Remembrance. Includes script material, location photographs, story boards, production files, shooting schedules, budget information, and historical research files.
Organization and Arrangement
There is no specific arrangement to the collection.
Related Material
Dan Curtis Productions Records (Collection PASC 1). Available UCLA Library Special Collections, Charles E. Young Research Library, UCLA.
Television production companies -- Archives.; ABC Circle Films -- Archives; Dan Curtis Productions
- Background information on characters (Box 2)
- Budget: Europe (Box 12)
- Budget information (Box 13, Box 14)
- Budgets - all departments (Box 18)
- Location lists for Europe and USA (Box 7)
- Location shots (Box 8, Box 9)
- Production files (Box 6, Box 7)
- WINDS OF WAR, 1983: production memoranda (1 folder) (Box 12)
- Research (Box 12)
- Research material (photocopies) on general and specific subjects and places (Box 10)
- Research material on German locations and history (Box 11)
- Section outline for documentary (Box 12)
- Script material (Box 2)
- Script material (Box 1)
- Scripts, parts I-VI (Box 15)
- Scripts, parts VII-IX (Box 16)
- Shooting schedules (Box 4)
- Shooting schedules (Box 3)
- Shooting schedule, 1st period, Jan - March 1986 (Box 16)
- Shooting schedule, 2nd period, March - June 1986 (Box 17)
- Shooting schedule, 3rd period, April - Sept 1986 (Box 17)
- Shooting schedule, 4th period, Oct - Dec 1986 (Box 18)
- Shooting schedule, 6th period, Feb - April 1987 (Box 18)
- Set Lists and set plans (Box 4)
- Story boards (Box 5)